Then will you help with my ideas?
I'd like you to make
bacon I can eat, Hank.
Bacon?!
And I want Riyah to fly.
Fly?!
Of course I'll pay you.
I think it's better than
wasting your time away, no?
O-Okay.
I'll do it, Kunon.
FLYING AND ROASTING AND BEING INVITED
Here's my new product,
the giant hairless rat.
For holding and going to sleep with?
Yes!
I received feedback that
if the pillow is different,
it can be harder to fall
asleep even on a water bed.
With this, you will fall
asleep no matter what.
Would you like to try?
I have a feeling I'll be obsessed
once I touch it, so I'll pass.
Are you sure?
And you?
I'll stay away as well.
Very well.
My sleeping beauties await,
so please excuse me.
It seems to be going well.
It's impressive.
He built such an efficient system
to make money in no time.
Reyes is doing well, too.
Hank and Riyah have started their
experiments thanks to Kunon's advice.
Today marks one month
since they enrolled here.
I suppose we don't need
to supervise them anymore.
A month, huh? Perhaps the
factions will make a move soon,
Is Kunon here?
I'd like to speak to him.
Me, too!
He just left.
What?!
Please excuse us.
They're on the move.
I can see a fierce battle already.
Now we have soft, smooth,
giant hairless rats.
The perfect companion
for your peaceful sleep!
A 60-minute course with the add-on!
I'll take a 90-minute course!
The business is doing well as usual.
A-ori.
You burned it again?
He's not here.
Where did he go?
Kunon?
I want you to make bacon
that can satisfy me soon.
I've never made bacon with
fire magic before, so...
Bacon is smoked for a long time,
rather than putting it on the fire.
I think it's possible if you
can maintain a constant heat.
I understand that,
but maintaining it for a
long time is difficult.
What is it?
Nothing.
Then you've got to try again.
Fu-ra.
Whoa!
Eek!
Kunon.
Th-Thank you, Kunon.
You need to figure out how
to float with stability first.
Right.
Here are your sandwiches.
The bacon's totally burnt...
Are you sure this is okay?
Yes. I can't let food go to waste.
You take responsibility
and eat these, too, Hank.
Sure.
May I have some as well?
I want to save up as much money as I can.
Of course.
Hank and I won't be able to finish
all these sandwiches ourselves.
Hello, Miss Reyes.
I never imagined you
would invite me to lunch!
May I talk about how
moved I am all day long?
No, thank you.
I don't have to pay when I go to lunch
with you, so I'm grateful for that.
This isn't... quite edible.
I'm sorry, but can I leave the bacon?
Miss Reyes!
Don't push yourself!
I'm sorry! I'm so ashamed!
So we should've waited for
him here to begin with.
Looking all over for him like an idiot.
Who are you calling an idiot?
Kunon.
I just pulled an all-nighter.
Sell me good sleep, now!
Thank you for requesting me,
my sleeping beauties and all of you.
Your Kunon has returned.
Oh, Kunon!
I'm first!
No, it's me!
Hey, don't cut in line!
I could collapse from
fatigue at any moment!
Sorry.
Thank you for waiting!
Which course would you like?
So the thing is, Kunon...
What is this?
A sinful add-on for princesses
who are in need of cradles,
to whisk them away to even better sleep.
That water bed itself
provided a sanctuary.
And now magic for even better rest...
What would you like to do?
There are three beds remaining.
Giant hairless rat...
I'm curious.
I want to try it.
Ka-shi.
It's easy to produce fire, but...
I think it's possible if you
can maintain a constant heat.
Easy for you to say.
Keep it low, keep it low.
Go higher.
Higher.
A new batch of shi-shilla, huh?
Professor Sureyya was raving about
the quality of your previous report.
Professor.
Yes?
I'm still not convinced.
Why is it necessary for us
to make money with magic?
Ever since you were small,
you all have only been doing experiments
and research on magic, right?
In society, there are
people who try to deceive
and take advantage of
naive sorcerers like you.
Magic is a special power given
only to the chosen people.
Our job is to foster sorcerers
who can use that power correctly
by making them work to
learn about society.
Did that convince you?
Yes.
Now it's Hank and Riyah's
turn to figure it out.
I hope it goes well for them.
They've got Kunon.
What?
He's frivolous, but I'm sure
they'll learn a lot from him.
Even though he's frivolous.
You're right.
Oh, recruiting for factions
has started today.
Did anyone come to see you?
No.
No one? What about Kunon?
That's strange.
This is strange.
No word from the students
I sent out for recruitment.
No need to rush.
It's only the first day.
You're right.
They're late.
Factions?
They're the organizations of the
students in the advanced class.
Among them, the three largest factions
are Ability, Harmony, and Rationality.
Students in the advanced class are
treated as full-fledged sorcerers, right?
Professors don't intervene
more than necessary.
So these are kind of like mutual
aid associations of students
who help each other when in need.
You know so much.
I used to be an assistant
to a professor here.
I'm not too interested,
since we're in a free environment and all.
But there are experiments that
require lots of help, you know?
Belonging to a faction
can be helpful then.
Doing experiments surrounded
by a lot of women, huh?
Recruitment was forbidden
for the first month so we
could get used to school life.
Apparently yesterday was the opening day.
Can we put in a request?
Yes. I'm thinking about joining Harmony.
I haven't picked one yet.
I'm still not sure, either.
ABILITY
Ability, Harmony, and Rationality, huh?
ABILITY, HARMONY
ABILITY, HARMONY, RATIONALITY
Anyways, shall we eat today's bacon?
I didn't burn it today.
I roasted it slowly on a low heat.
Thank you for the food.
It's so salty!
Why?! Was it the heat control?
You've gotta try again.
What exactly did you do all day yesterday?
I-I'm so sorry.
Did that work?
Representative, that tone really suits you.
Like a Demon Lord!
I'll have you know that this
is rather against my will.
You couldn't recruit him?
I'm sorry, representative.
I fell asleep.
You fell asleep...?
I just couldn't resist his magic.
His giant hairless rat?
His giant hairless rat.
Oh, I see.
As expected of Zeonly's student, I suppose.
Hello, Bael and Shilto.
What brings you here?
Stop acting so innocent.
Sorry, but I have no intention
of letting you go first.
Same here.
Then shall we decide on the
order fair and square?
I'm so tired.
Don't you want the incentive fee?
And the credits?
Way to prey on my vulnerability.
If you ask me,
I think you're the problematic one here,
trying to get paid for a half-baked job.
A critical hit with a fair argument.
Fine, I'll do it.
Fu-ra.
How are you doing, Riyah?
I'm getting the hang of floating.
Then let's try moving.
A-ori.
Wow! Is this the same as the water bed?
Yes, because it's dangerous if you fall.
There must be no water
Kunon can't produce.
Born to the house of a
baron in countryside,
I was called the best
sorcerer in nation...
Fu-garu.
People thought I was a
future Royal Sorcerer,
but I was a big fish in a small pond.
Shall we begin?
Are you ready, young man?
For now, I have to be able to make money.
For the sake of my father who
scraped together the tuition for me,
and my entire family.
Yeah, I'm ready!
I will record everything, from you
flying to falling and tumbling.
Don't write about me falling and tumbling.
Okay, fine. I'll change that
to "he spoke to a girl."
Oh, then you can say I fell and tumbled.
Is that also a magic
experiment over there?
He successfully completed the
school's assignment in a few tries.
His skills are a better fit for
our Ability faction, I'd say!
I hear he has a capacity for teamwork,
giving advice to his classmates.
Harmony is the best fit for him!
Being a Hero's Scar, and given his
exceptional magic that even
made Zeonly acknowledge
him as a student,
it's only rational that he
joins Rationality.
That looks fun.
Is it too weak?
But high heat will burn it again.
Shall I keep it low?
So, high heat? High or low...?
Are you going to leave it uncooked now?
That's a boring failure.
But this is fire.
What else can I do other
than low or high heat?
You were an assistant to a
professor for a long time, right?
Yeah, and I was diligent.
I learned the basics and
gained lots of knowledge.
Then why aren't you
trying anything crafty?
That's what I've been waiting for.
You're not an assistant anymore,
so you can let yourself be free.
Fire can have smell or different colors.
What? Fire with smell and colors?
Surprise me.
Try every possible means and show
me your little magic tricks.
I'm sure you can, Hank.
Hey, Kunon!
Give that rat of yours
to this professor, stat!
My goodness. Why do you push yourself
until you get to this state?
But... my research...
Understood! A-ori.
Kunon!
Is that what Zeonly taught you?
No, my first teacher.
She taught me that creativity
was a form of talent.
She yelled at me for calling
her magic "little tricks."
Magic is free, huh?
Fire of a different color...
Fire with smell.
A smell that fits bacon.
Wood chips?
No, hold on.
If I can add colors and
smells, why not flavors?
If I add flavor to the aroma of
herbs, it should work... Okay!
Oh, I see. This is how one experiments.
I worked as an assistant
for so long that I forgot.
Experiments allow you to try many things.
I've got to surprise him and
get the incentive fee.
Hey, Hank.
Would you like to join Harmony?
Whoa?!
Stop, stop!
Oh man, I fell and tumbled.
You lose balance because you're
trying to forcibly control the wind.
Try doing it as if you're going along
with the wind, like you're following it.
Th-Thank you very much.
It's actually not bad.
Right. I like that it
has aroma and a flavor.
You did it, Hank!
Yes!
It doesn't make me nauseous, and my body
doesn't reject it as a foreign object.
Let's keep this up and try
bacon of different meats.
I knew you'd say that.
Bacon of fish, chicken, and mutton!
You made all this, Hank?
Fish is my favorite.
This is incredible.
You surprised me!
But I can't eat this much.
Oops.
At this quality, I'm happy
to purchase them from you.
Looking forward to more tomorrow!
Yes! Thank you very much!
Did you manage to fly, Riyah?
Yes. I got advice from an
upperclassman in Rationality.
I can't fly too far yet, though.
Once you can successfully
fly long distances,
I think you can use it to
start a courier service.
I see. That can be a business.
Thank you, Kunon! I'll do my best!
Of course! And let me
write a report on it!
By the way, I was invited to join
Rationality when I got the advice.
And I think I'm going to do that.
She was cute.
I was invited to Harmony.
I was invited to Ability,
but I'm not sure about it.
What? Then I'm the only one
who hasn't been invited.
Oh.
With you, Kunon...
I think they're fighting over you.
I think so, too.
I agree.
Are you saying girls are fighting over me?
The right of the first negotiation with
Kunon Gurion is the Ability faction's!
Harmony will go second.
So Rationality goes third?
Very well.
It does give you advantage to negotiate
first, but he's the one who chooses.
Lulu was at a disadvantage in
terms of his attributes.
I feel bad you.
I agreed to the conditions,
so I won't make excuse.
You're on, the biggest boy
magnet of the faction.
Sure thing, Mr. Bael!
NEXT TIME: FAIRIES CHECKING THE ANSWER
Next episode: "Fairies
Checking the Answer."